https://www.lancasterarchery.com/privacy-policy/

Academy
Log OutRecurve BowsFormula Olympic Recurve Risers & LimbsILF Olympic Recurve RisersILF Olympic Recurve LimbsILF Take-Down RisersILF Take-Down LimbsILF Take-Down BowsTake-Down RisersTake-Down LimbsTake-Down Recurve BowsTake-Down LongbowsOne-Piece Recurve BowsOne-Piece LongbowsBow PackagesYouth BowsCompound BowsRecurve BowsLongbowsCompound Bow PackagesRecurve Bow PackagesCrossbowsCrossbow PackagesBowfishingCompound PackagesRecurve PackagesBow AccessoriesFeatured ProductsNew ArrivalsStaff PicksClearanceSights, Scopes & PeepsHunting SightsCompound 3D & Target SightsRecurve Target SightsSight Accessories3D & Target ScopesScope LensesScope AccessoriesRecurve Sight Pins & AperturesSight Lights & BatteriesSight Scales & SoftwarePeep Sights & AccessoriesStabilizersTarget StabilizersHunting StabilizersSide RodsV-Bar ExtensionsStabilizer WeightsQuick DisconnectsV-Bar MountsOffset & Side MountsVibration Reduction DampersStabilizer PartsNoise ReductionWrist SlingsGrips & AccessoriesGripsOther AccessoriesArrow Rests, Plungers & ClickersCompound Hunting RestsCompound Target RestsRecurve & Finger RestsBowfishing RestsPlungersClickersTraditional Rests / RugsArrow Rest AccessoriesPlunger AccessoriesClicker AccessoriesBow Strings & AccessoriesBow Strings & CablesCrossbow Strings & CablesBowstring MaterialString Serving ThreadString / Serving Jigs & Tools Instructional VideosNok Sets & Kisser ButtonsPeep Sights & AccessoriesString Silencers & AccessoriesBow String WaxLoop RopeCable Guards & Cable SlidesDraw StopsBow Tip ProtectorsBow Cases & CoversHard Compound CasesSoft Compound CasesHard Take-Down Recurve CasesSoft Take-Down Recurve CasesRecurve BackpacksSoft One Piece Recurve CasesHard Crossbow CasesSoft Crossbow CasesRiser, Limbs & Stabilizer CoversBow Case Covers & AccessoriesCrossbow AccessoriesCocking DevicesNoise ReductionRail LubeSlingsShooting SticksOther AccessoriesBowfishing AccessoriesPackagesReelsLineGaffsOther AccessoriesAccessory PackagesCompound Accessory PackagesRecurve Accessory PackagesCrossbow Accessory PackagesRecurve Bow Hardware & PartsCams & ModulesArrowsFeatured ProductsNew ArrivalsStaff PicksClearanceArrow ShaftsTarget & 3D ShaftsHunting ShaftsTraditional ShaftsYouth & Beginner ShaftsFletched ArrowsTarget & 3D ArrowsHunting ArrowsTraditional ArrowsYouth & Beginner ArrowsCrossbow Bolts / Arrows Bowfishing ArrowsArrow ComponentsNocksLighted NocksCrossbow NocksNock Pins & BushingsNock CollarsVanesFeathersGlue-In PointsScrew-In PointsScrew-In InsertsGlue-On PointsGlue-On OutsertsPoint WeightsArrow WrapsArrow NumbersArrow Building & RepairAdhesives, Glue & EpoxyFletching JigsArrow Cut-Off SawsToolsGrain ScalesArrow StraightnersFeather CuttersFeather TreatmentArrow Selection SoftwareBroadheads & Specialty PointsFixed Blade BroadheadsExpandable BroadheadsHybrid BroadheadsCrossbow BroadheadsTraditional BroadheadsTurkey BroadheadsReplacement BladesSmall Game PointsBowfishing PointsBlunt PointsSharpeners & ToolsBroadhead StorageArrow Tubes & CasesTargetsFeatured ProductsNew ArrivalsStaff PicksClearanceArchery TargetsTarget FacesRange TargetsTarget Cores / InsertsBlock & Foam TargetsBag TargetsBag Covers3D Targets3D Inserts / MidsectionsNovelty TargetsCrossbow TargetsTarget RepairRange EquipmentTiming & Scoring SystemsTarget PinsTarget StandsBow Hangers / StandsShooting StakesBackstop NettingTarget FlagsShooting GearFeatured ProductsNew ArrivalsStaff PicksClearanceReleases & AccessoriesHandheld Trigger ReleasesBack Tension ReleasesResistance Activated ReleasesIndex Finger ReleasesRelease StrapsRelease AccessoriesRelease BagsRelease & Loop RopeGuards, Gloves & TabsArmguardsChest Guards / ProtectorsShooting GlovesFinger TabsFinger Tab AccessoriesFinger & Wrist SlingsQuivers & AccessoriesTarget & 3D QuiversYouth QuiversQuiver BeltsBelt & Quiver AccessoriesBow Rests / CarriersHunting Bow QuiversHunting Side QuiversTraditional Back QuiversShooting AccessoriesArrow LubeArrow PullersChairs & StoolsBow Stands / HoldersScore Card Holders / PunchesUmbrellasOptics & RangefindersBinocularsMonocularsRangefindersSpotting ScopesCrossbow OpticsOptics AccessoriesShooting GlassesTools & TrainingFeatured ProductsNew ArrivalsStaff PicksClearanceToolsBow Presses & AccessoriesBow VisesLevels & Leveling ToolsBow ScalesDraw BoardsChronographsPaper TunersNock & D-Loop PliersBow SquaresMulti-ToolsHex & Torx SetsTool KitsBow StringersOil & LubricantsOther ToolsHow-To DVDsHow-To BooksTrainingStretchbands & ExercisersShot Training AidsTraining DVDsTraining BooksLancaster Archery AcademyArchery Courses & SeminarsNASP® Approved EquipmentGenesis BowsBow MaintenanceArrow MaintenanceFinger Tabs, Gloves & ArmguardsQuivers & Bow CasesTargetsRange EquipmentDecal KitsOlympic Archery in SchoolsHuntingFeatured ProductsNew ArrivalsStaff PicksClearanceHunting AccessoriesSaws & PrunersKnivesKnife SharpenersFlashlights & HeadlampsInsect RepellentWind CheckerBow Hangers / HoldersBow Slings / CarriersGame CartsElectric Bikes & AccessoriesCoolersCooler AccessoriesEveryday Bags & GearOther AccessoriesCamerasTrail / Game Cameras Bow & Action CamerasCamera AccessoriesNavigation & CommunicationTwo-Way RadiosCompassesTrail MarkersPortable PowerHunting DVDsHunting BooksTree Stands & BlindsClimbing Tree StandsHang-On Tree StandsLadder Tree StandsTree Steps & Climbing SticksSafety Harnesses & AccessoriesGround BlindsTree Stand & Blind AccessoriesPacksBackpacks & Fanny PacksHydration BladdersDuffel BagsScent ControlScent Elimination SpraysClothing Wash & PrepShampoo & Body WashFoot & Underarm DeodorantBreath Odor EliminationLotionElectronic Scent EliminationGame CallsDeer CallsRattle Bags / HornsTurkey CallsElk CallsScents & LurePre-Rut LuresRut LuresCover ScentsElk ScentLure DispensersFood AttractantsDecoysDeer DecoysTurkey DecoysPredator DecoysWildlife ManagementFood Plot SeedMineral SupplementsClothingFeatured ProductsNew ArrivalsStaff PicksClearanceLancaster Archery ApparelHatsShirtsOuterwearFootwearHunting FootwearCasual ApparelHatsShirtsOuterwearAccessoriesManufacturer ApparelBackpacksHunting ApparelCamo ClothingScent Elimination Clothing Heated ClothingBaselayer ClothingRain WearHeadwearGloves & SocksFace CamoOutletFeatured ProductsNew ArrivalsStaff PicksClearanceSaleMonthly SpecialsCurrent DealsClearanceJust ReducedHot BuysOpen BoxBy Brand30-06 Outdoors8Bplus3D CountryA-Way Hunting ProductsA&D ArcheryAAEAccu-ArcheryAccuBowAce Archery TackleACU ArcheryAddicted To The OutdoorsAdvanced TreestandsAfflictor BroadheadsAim OutdoorsAkaiAkusta ArcheryAl HendersonAlaska Bowhunting SupplyAll-Blade ArcheryAll-In OutdoorsAllenAllen-PalAllied ArcheryAlpen OpticsAlpine ArcheryAlpine InnovationsALPS OutdoorZAuto LightAmboAmerica's Best BowstringsAmerican LeathersAmerican WhitetailAmeristepAMS BowfishingAngelAntler Action ProductsAnthony CameraApex GearAPI OutdoorsAppleArc RolanArcher XtremeArcher's AdvantageArchers AfieldArchery Game CubeArchery GBArchery Shot ExecutionArchery SquadArcTecArctic ShieldAREArizona Rim CountryArrowhead, U.K.ArrowmatArrow BrakeArrow PerflectionArrow PrecisionASAT OutdoorsASES ArcheryAstra ArcheryAthens ArcheryAtomic RodsAtskoAuroraAutumn Warrior OutdoorsAvalon ArcheryAvian-XAxcelAXE BroadheadsAxe Crossbows by FeraDyneAxionB3 ArcheryBadger BroadheadsBadlandsBAI ArcheryBaker Archery ProductsBaremaxBargeBarnettBarronett BlindsBarskaBCYBe The DecoyBear ArcheryBearpawBee StingerBeier DistributionBeiterBemanBen'sBenders No-GlovBernie’s Control FreakBi-Delta VanesBig & JBig Dog TreestandsBig Foot CamerasBig Game TreestandsBig GreenBig Rock ArcheryBignamiBIGshotBill Langer Bowhunting ProductionsBioShieldBitzenburgerBJORN BengtsonBlack Diamond EquipmentBlack EagleBlack GoldBlack Hole TargetsBlack Mamba ArcheryBlack Mountain OutfittersBlack WidowBlacks CreekBlaze ArcheryBlaze PublishingBlazerBlock TargetsBlood Therapy BroadheadsBloodsportBlue OtterBob FrommeBob KirschnerBob Smith IndustriesBob's ArcheryBobble Head ToysBodoodleBOGBohningBoldoducBomarBonus RingBoosterBorder Crossing ScentsBow ChicBow LifeBow Medic ArcheryBowAdxBowfingerBowfitBowHitch ArcheryBowhunt or DieBowjaxBowmarBowmasterBowTechBowtreeBrad IshamBreath TakerBresserBrian SorrellsBrim ClipsBrite SiteBrownellBrowningBruntonBuff HeadwearB.U.P. SportsBuck Bomb ScentsBuck KnivesBuck Rub GearBuck StopBuck WearBuckCageBuckshotGearBurrisBushnellBushnell Performance FootwearByron FergusonC-EZ Reflective Outdoor ProductsC.R. Archery ProductsC.W. EricksonC'Mere DeerCaldwellCajun BowfishingCamoWrapsCampbell GirlsCAMXCanCookerCapture Your HuntCarbon ExpressCarbon ImpactCarbon TechCarbonProCarsonCartelCarterCascade ArcheryCatchin' DeersCBECDM FlitemateCelestronCenterPoint ArcheryCentral Wisconsin CenterChampion Custom BowstringsCherryhill OutdoorsChris Charleston OutdoorsChronotirCir-CutCirrus OutdoorsClear TargetsClearshot ArcheryClint FreemanClub RedCM SackettCoach Kim, Hyung TakCoastCobraCode BlueCoffey MarketingCold SteelCole Outdoor ProductionsColemanCompass 360Competition Archery MediaCompetition Archery ProductsCompetition ElectronicsConquest ArcheryConQuest ScentsCoop's BowsmithCopper JohnCore 4 ElementCore ArcheryCottonwood OutdoorsCovert Scouting CamerasCranfordCrooked HornCrosspoint ArcheryCross-XCuddebackCustom Arrow Wraps.comCyclopsDaisyDalton Archery ProductsDamascusDamon HowattDan BertalanDanageDave CousinsDay 6 OutdoorsDead CenterDead Down WindDead On TraditionalDead Ringer Deadeye OutfittersDeborah CharlesDecut ArcheryDeer SkeetDelta McKenzieDelta Sports Products Denise ParkerDiamond ArcheryDirect Outdoor ProductsDirtNap GearDoc's Deer ScentsDoinkerDouble BullDouble Vision ArcheryDoug SchlabachDoyle's Deer GearDP SleevesDragon SpitDrake's AdventuresDraves ArcheryDrury OutdoorsDry Fire ArcheryDryad BowsDUEL Game CallsDuracellDuraMesh Archery TargetsDynamic ArcheryE. W. BatemanEagle's Flight ArcheryEarlyhumanEaston OutfittersEastonEasy-EyeEclipse BroadheadsEklindElevationElevatorsElimaTreeElite ArcheryEliVanesElk Ridge ArcheryElvish Tac Innovative Outdoor ProductsEP HuntingEpekEPICEpic ArcheryEvolved HabitatsEvolved HarvestExcaliburEXEExtremeExtreme Hunting SolutionsEyeBlackEZ KUTNose JammerFast FletchFairweather ArcheryFeather River SportsFeather VisionFedoraFiberbowField and StreamField LogicFieldlineFieldsheerFin-FinderFirenockFirst LiteFirstStringFivicsFlambeauFleetwoodFletcher ArcheryFlex ArcheryFlex-FletchFlexor ArcheryFlextoneFlying Arrow ArcheryFMJ DesignsFogZeroForEverlastFourth Arrow Camera ArmsFred EichlerFreddie ArcheryFrogg ToggsFUSEFuzzy Stuff FleeceG5 OutdoorsG. Fred AsbellGadget Grabbers OutdoorsGalaxy ArcheryGamekeeperGame Warning SystemsGameFaceGamePlan GearGarminGary StudtGAS BowstringsGas ProGateway FeathersGearhead ArcheryGene Brehm ProductionsGenesis ArcheryGeorge Ryals IVGerberGerbing'sGerman Precision OpticsGibbs Archery GearGilloGlacier OutdoorsGlenDel TargetsGlenrock ArcheryGlo-WrapGloersGloryNockGoat TuffGold RingGold TipGoProGorilla GearGorilla TapeGorilla TreestandsGray ArcheryGraylingGreat DayGreat NorthernGreatree ArcheryGreene Mountain OutdoorsGrim ReaperGrime BossGripper ArcheryGrizzly CoolersGum-O-FlageGutCheckGunstarGV SystemsH.E.C.S. Human Energy ConcealmentHalo OpticsHammer HangerHamskeaHardy FacepaintHardy WardHavalon KnivesHAWKHawke Sport OpticsHawgLiteHeDog ArcheryHeads Up DecoysHeartAway Hunting ProductsHeat FactoryHeat MaxHeater Body SuitHero Outdoor ProductsHHA SportsHi-Tek ArcheryHi Mountain SeasoningsHicks PlasticHigdon OutdoorsHigh Demand ArcheryHigh FiveHigh Point ProductsHind SightHips TargetsHitmen GearHMEHold Up DisplaysHooyman SawsHorn HunterHortonHotHandsHot ShotHot Shot TacticalHoytHTMHunga MungaHunor ArcheryHunt ComfortHunter DanHunter Safety SystemHunters SpecialtiesHuntimeHurricane TargetsHushPukHybridLightHydro FlaskIce Cold TowelsIHunt CommunicationsIllusion SystemsImpact ArcheryInsightsInfitec ArcheryInnerlocInnovative Archery ProductsInterMedia OutdoorsInvisible HunterIQ BowsightsIWOM OuterwearIronCladJ & D BowstringsJ&J WrapsJacob AshJager ArcheryJames ParkJanDao CrossbowsJay KidwellJim RebuckJohn DudleyJoJanJust be NaturalJVD DistributionK VanesK-ThumpK&K ArcheryKabuki StrengthKanati QuiversKantPinchKathy Kelly DesignKAYA ArcheryKeyes Hunting GearKillbillies OutdoorsKiller Food PlotsKiller InstinctKimsha ArcheryKineticKinex SystemsKisik LeeKlawhorne IndustriesKnight & HaleKodiakKoola BuckKristen SchmittKrossen ArcheryKruger OpticalKTechKudlacekKustom KingKurly VanesKwikee KwiverLA Hunting GearLaCrosseLakewood ProductsLancaster Archery SupplyLanskyLarry WiseLAS Custom Strings LAS DistributionLast Chance ArcheryLaunchtecLeatherman ToolLebrunetLED LenserLegacy LeatherLegend ArcheryLeicaLenhart ReleasesLethalLeupoldLeverage TreestandsLiam GrimwoodLiberty MountainLimbSaverLizard SkinsLOC OutdoorZLone WolfLowdownLP Archery CompanyLP Archery ProductsLucky BuckLucky StopsLumenokLVE DecalsMagEyesMagic FixMagnacraftMagnusMake-Up IndustriesMantis Tech ManzellaMaple LeafMarcoMardenMarky SparkyMarshmallow Fun CompanyMartinMasterpiece Archery TargetsMasterTargetMatch Point ArcheryMaurice ThompsonMaverick BlindsMaxFlashMaximusMD-50 GearMDR Outdoor GroupMegaBOOMMental Management SystemMeoptaMerlin ArcheryMG ProductsMichael Braden ArcheryMichele FrangilliMid Atlantic ArcheryMidlandMike HolsonMike MittenMillennium TreestandsMission ArcheryMission CrossbowsMK ArcheryMoccasin Joe "Ambush Products"Montana DecoyMontana SilversmithsMOR Archery TargetMorin TrainerMorrellMoultrieMountain Man FursMountain Mike's ReproductionMr. HeaterMTM Case-GardMTN OPSMuck BootsMudCat BowfishingMuddyMuzzyMy Bow BuddyMyboName The GameNapp's ArcheryNature VisionNEBO ToolsNeetNAP-New Archery ProductsNative Ground BlindsNew Dawn OutdoorsNiceTargetsNikonNo Frontiers ArcheryNo Limit ArcheryNock On GearNock OutNockturnalNomadNorth American WhitetailNorthern Broadheads NZNuFletch ArcheryNxt GenerationO2COOLOak Ridge ArcheryObsession BowsOctaneOctober Mountain ProductsOl' Man TreestandsOld MountainOmega Bow SightsOne Source OutfittersOnX Hunt AppOpti-LogicOsborn'sOutdoor DecalsOutdoor Edge CutleryOutdoor ProstaffOuter LimitOzark FeatherOzcut BroadheadsOzonicsP&A ArcheryParkerParris ManufacturingPDPPEET DryerPelican CasePetersen's BowhuntingPFI Inc Z BladePhone SkopePilla Performance EyewearPine RidgePinnacle ArcheryPinwheel SoftwarePlanoPole Mountain OutdoorsPope & Young ClubPower-Stop Archery TargetsPower BalancePower CallsPrairie InnovatorsPrecision Archery ReticlesPrecision BalancePressure Perfect ProductsPrimePrimitives By KathyPrimosPrinceton TecPro ReleasePromier ProductsPyro PuttyPSEPX2 BroadheadsQ2i ArcheryQADQALOQuality Archery ProductsQuestQuietKatQuick CrestQuick MittQuick OneQuiver Archery ApparelR.A.D.R.S. BowviseR&W TargetsRack OneRageRAM ProductsRamcatRamRodsRange-O-MaticRanger Ready RepellentRaptoRazorRattler GripsRaven OutdoorsRavin CrossbowsRay AshfordReactor TacticalReal AvidRealWildRealtreeRecon ArcheryReconyxRed Hawk ArcheryRenzoRhino BlindsRhino OutdoorsRichard CockrellRick WelchRick Young Outdoors RinehartRipcordRivers Edge TreestandsRobinhood VideosRocket BroadheadsRockyRocky MountainRogue BowstringsRon Bushong WaxRose CityRough RidgeRUGIDRuko ProductsRusted Rooster MediaRuth RoweS4 GearS.A.F.E. ArcherySaberSABOSack UpsSafari TuffSamickSanford InnovationsSanLiDa Archery SA SportsSaundersSawtooth Outdoor ProductsScentLokScent Control SystemsScent CrusherScent BlockerScent SmokerSchliteScorpion VenomScott ArcheryScrapeFixScrapeStickSeal 1Seek ThermalSeirusSelway ArcherySF ArcheryShehawken ArcheryShibuyaShooter 3D TargetsShore Shot ArcheryShrewdSICHTKRAFT Archery ScoreboardsSiegfried ReleaseSignature Products GroupSIK BroadheadsSimon S. NeedhamSITKASKBSkipjackSkull HookerSkulTatsSky ArcherySlate RiverSlayer BroadheadsSlick TrickSmith'sSmoke in a BottleSmokin RackSOCXSolid Broadhead CompanySpartan CameraSpecialtySpider ArcherySpider VanesSpigarelliSpinPINSpirit ArcherySports SensorsSportsman's Outdoor ProductsSpot HoggSpyderWebSPYPOINTSqwincherSRT TargetsStark ArcherySTANStealth CamSteel ForceSterner DutteraSteve RuisStic-N-PicStick & String OutfittersStokerizedStone MountainStoney-Wolf ProductionsStorm Archery STOS ArcheryStreamlightStrickland's ArcheryStrotherStrykerSTS ArcherySugruSummitSunsectSuperior Archery DesignSURE-LOCSWAT BroadheadsSwhackerSwordSynunm ArcheryT.J. ConradsT.R.U. BallT-Bird ArcheryTAC VanesTactacamTactical Archery SystemsTarantula Archery Target Plot SoftwareTATS SystemTeam FitzgeraldTeam OverkillTenPointTenzing Terry Arrow RestTerry WunderleThe Archery ProgramThe Bowyers EdgeThe SchwackerThe Tarsal WickThermacellThermaSeatThird HandThompson TargetThorn ArcheryThunder Valley ArcheryTight LiteTightSpotTilt TamerTimber CreekTimberline ArcheryTink'sTitan 3DTitan ScopesTom DorigattiTooth of the ArrowTopHatTop Secret Deer ScentsTotal PeepTowne Hall ArcheryToxon TechnologiesTraditional Bowyers BibleTraditional Vision QuestTradTech ArcheryTree SpiderTree Stand UpTreelimbTribe ArcheryTrophy Blend ScentsTrophy RidgeTrophy TakerTru-FireTrue North OutdoorsTrue SpotTrue Timber CamoTrueflightTruGloTruProductsTurbowSpeedTwin Valley ProductionsU-nique Archery ProductsUltraView ArcheryUnder ArmourUSA ArcheryUukhaVan Handle Archery ProductsVan WebsterVaneTecVanguardVanishVantage Point Archery (VPA)VaporTrailVeteran Innovative ProductsVibracheckVictoryVikingViperViscosity BowstringsVistaVital XVivid ArcheryVolt ResistanceVortex OpticsWac'Em ArcheryWalker's Game EarWartorn ArcheryWaspWaterloo ArcheryWatsonWensel Brothers DVDWestern RecreationWestonWhitetail'RWhitetail AdrenalineWhitetail InstituteWhitewater Creek ProductsWhitewater OutdoorsWicked RidgeWicked Tree GearWifler IndustriesWildgame InnovationsWildlife Research CenterWii GamesWildviewWin & WinWinchesterWinn ArcheryWinners ArcheryWinner's Choice BowstringsWoodsmanWoody's LubeWoodyweightsWork SharpX-Focus 365X Sight ArcheryX-Brand ArcheryX-FactorX-SpotX-Stand TreestandsXS WingsXecutioner BroadheadsXtreme Outdoor Products (XOP)YETIYo' BuddyYost ArcheryYoung Feather BurnerZbros ArcheryZebra BowstringsZeissZenith Archery ProductsZingZink CallsZniper ArcheryZwickey ArcheryMathews More
Featured
Articles & Videos
Account Lancaster Archery Classic - Register Today!
|
Free Shipping on Orders of $99 or More! - Ends 12/14!
Privacy Policy
Home
Lancaster Archery Supply Privacy Policy
Effective Date: 05/24/2018
This Privacy Policy describes how Lancaster Archery Supply Inc. (“Lancaster Archery”, “we”,
“our”, or “us”) collects, uses, and shares personal information of users of this website, www.lancasterarchery.com or www.lancasterarcherydealer.com (the
“Site”). We periodically update this Privacy Policy and reserve the right to change the provisions of this
Policy or our privacy practices at any time. If you subscribe to Lancaster Archery, then you will receive notice
when this Privacy Policy is modified. If not, then we encourage you to review this site periodically and we will
alert you that changes have been made by updating the Effective Date of the Policy. Your use of the Site
constitutes consent to any changes in this Policy as in effect on the date of such use.
Your Rights to Access Your Personal Information
You have the right to access personal information about you that Lancaster Archery has collected through this
Site by sending a request for access to support@lancasterarchery.com.
You can also request that we correct or delete any such information by sending an email to the same address.
To verify that the request is authentic, we may require that such request be sent from the email address
associated with your personal information. While we will comply reasonably and promptly with your request,
we may need to retain some of your information for our own record keeping or to fulfill a legal obligation.
If you are a subscriber to Lancaster Archery, you may correct, update, or remove your information by making
the change on your user account settings page, or by emailing our Customer Support Team at support@lancasterarchery.com. If you no longer desire
our services, please contact us directly.
What is personal information?
Personal information means information that specifically identifies an individual person, such as name,
mailing address, email address, phone number, or account number. It may also include other information about
you, such as gender, date of birth, or other demographic information, or about your use of the Site, such as
IP address or cookies, if that other information is linked to your personal information.
How your information is collected
Lancaster Archery collects personal information that you provide to us. For example:
If you sign up for Lancaster Archery’s services, Lancaster Archery may require you to register by
providing your name, email address, phone number, and other information. You may be asked to create a
username and password to login to our website.
If you apply for a job with Lancaster Archery, we may ask you to provide more detailed and sensitive
personal information required for compliance with our hiring and equal opportunity policies and
practices.
Our website includes social media features, such as links to our Facebook, YouTube and Twitter pages.
Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Our website also includes customer reviews where we may post information with your consent.
We also collect some of your information automatically when you visit or log on to this Site. For example,
this Site collects your IP address and other online identifiers and records the pages that you visit and
other information about your activity on the Site.
Like many other websites, we ask you to allow us to use “cookies” to remember information about you and
improve your browsing experience on our Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your
ability to use some features or areas of our Site may be limited. We may also work with third-party
providers who may use cookies on our Site. You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser
that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. For more information about cookies, including
how to set your internet browser to reject cookies, please go to www.allaboutcookies.org
or www.networkadvertising.org.
What we do with your information
Lancaster Archery may use your personal information to:
provide products and services;
send requested product or service information;
send marketing communication;
send you emails or otherwise respond to questions, concerns, and customer support inquiries;
create demographic profiles of our subscribers, clients, and visitors to target our email alerts and
website marketing; or
improve the services we offer you or the functionality of our Site.
Lancaster Archery does not sell personal information to third parties and does not transfer or share
customers’ personal information. Lancaster Archery will share your personal information only:
With your consent;
to fulfill a legal obligation, including:
- in response to lawful requests or legal process, including in response to law enforcement requirements; or
- as part of a business transaction, sale or transfer, or bankruptcy proceeding;
for protection of personal or public safety or to prevent illegal activities;
to protect our own rights including enforcing our own policies, contracts, and terms of use.
Lancaster Archery may also use anonymous or pseudonymous personal information for internal purposes, such as
to monitor the performance of its platform, or to track the effectiveness of and improve its products,
processes, or services. Lancaster Archery may also share anonymous or pseudonymous data with selected third
parties.
Note: We understand our emails may not always be relevant, for your convenience, an unsubscribe link is
included at the bottom of each email. You may also manage your email preferences at any time by visiting http://www.lancasterarchery.com/preference-center.
How Lancaster Archery Protects Personal Information
Lancaster Archery follows generally accepted standards to protect personal information and information
submitted by our customers, both during transmission and once we receive it. Lancaster Archery maintains all
customers in carrier-class secure facilities protected by firewalls and other security devices. These
measures are designed to protect visitor and customer information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized
alteration. Lancaster Archery employs various information security mechanisms and internal policies and
procedures to protect information from disclosure to unauthorized third parties. Lancaster Archery routinely
audits its practices and policies to meet industry standards for data protection. Lancaster Archery provides
an SSL encrypted, password-protected mechanism for logging in, viewing, uploading, and extracting customer
data.
Personal information provided to Lancaster Archery by its customers remains the property of its
customers.
Who to Contact
To report any issues or concerns, or to contact Lancaster Archery with any questions regarding this Privacy
Policy, email us at support@lancasterarchery.com, or call
800.829.7408.
You may also contact us as follows:
Fax: 717.556.1390
Postal Address: Lancaster Archery Supply, 21 Graybill Rd, Leola, PA 17540
